(ナルト)なんだってばよ？ この絵…。
What's up with...this picture?
変な絵…。
(サクラ)この絵本…➡
This is a strange picture.
In this picture book...
真ん中の 見開きのページだけ
描きかけなの…。
only the facing pages
in the middle are incomplete...
これ… なんか 気味悪いってばよ。
This is...kind of creepy...
ナルト！
Naruto!
今度こそ…➡
This time for sure...
we'll save Sasuke!
私たちで サスケ君を！
あぁ！
Right!
(サスケ)遅かったな…。
You're late.
午後から 新術の修業に➡
Weren't you supposed
to join me
for some new Jutsu training
this afternoon, Orochimaru?
つきあうって話じゃ なかったか？
大蛇丸。
(カブト)また そんな言葉遣いを…。
Talking rude like that again...
(大蛇丸)そう 怒らないで…。
Don't get so angry.
かわりに 今日は➡
Instead, I got a little present
for you today...
ちょっとした プレゼントが
手に入ってね…。
This is a Shinobi from the Leaf,
just like you...
(大蛇丸)あなたと同じ
木ノ葉出身の 忍…。
(大蛇丸)懐かしい ふるさと話でも
できるんじゃなくて？
You guys should be able
to exchange...
nostalgic stories of home, right?
フンッ…。
《サイ : うちは… サスケ…》
Sasuke... Uchiha...
Infiltration:
The Den of the Snake!
はじめまして。
ボクは サイと言います。
How do you do?
My name is Sai.
キミが うちは サスケ君で…。
失せろ…。
So you're Sasuke Uchiha--?
Get lost.
笑顔を 作ってはみても➡
It seems I'm the type of person
people don't like one way or another...
ボクは 何かと
嫌われやすいタイプみたいだ…。
even if I try to make a smile...
ナルト君にも
嫌われたばかりだってのに…。
Just recently,
Naruto also expressed
his dislike towards me...
でも… ナルト君と比べると➡
But I get the feeling
I'll be able...
to get along better with you
compared to Naruto.
キミのほうが
なかよく できそうなんだけどな。
サスケ君!!
Sasuke!
汗…。
I'm sweating...?
《何も 感じない…。
I don't feel anything...
and I have no emotions.
感情のない ボクが
目を 見合わせただけで…➡
Yet just by looking
into Sasuke's eyes...
I feared him within the depths of my soul
that even I can't perceive?
自分でも 認識できない
心の 奥底で➡
サスケ君を 恐れたというのか!?》
あまり サスケ君を
おちょくらないほうが いいわよ。
It's probably not a good idea...
to joke around
with Sasuke too much.
He's even more troublesome
than I am, you see.
私より 厄介だからね…。
I don't care about that guy.
そんなヤツは どうでもいい。
これから すぐ つきあえ。 大蛇丸。
Join me right now...
Orochimaru.
I've heard a lot about you
from Naruto.
(サイ)キミのことは
ナルト君から いろいろ聞いてます。
キミのことを
ずっと 捜していたみたいだ。
It seems he was looking for you
over the last three years...
この ３年間…。
いたな… そんなヤツも…。
There used to be
a guy like that...wasn't there?
Let's go, Orochimaru.
いくぞ 大蛇丸。
(サイ)ナルト君は キミのことを…。
Naruto said he thinks of you like...
キミのことを
本当の兄弟のように思ってると➡
He thinks of you like
a real brother...
そう サクラさんから聞きました。
That's what I heard from Sakura.
オレの兄弟は 殺したい男…➡
I only have...one brother...
the man I want to kill.
ただ１人だけだ。
じゃあ 私も行くわ。
Okay, I'll be going, too.
Kabuto... make a Bingo Book
using this.
カブト これで
ビンゴブックを作っておきなさい。
はい。
Yes, sir.
じゃあ あとはお願い。
Then, I leave the rest to you.
これは…!?
What's this?
火影直轄部隊
暗部構成員リストの写しか…。
A copy of the list
of Anbu Black Ops members...
under the direct command
of the Hokage...?
(カブト)どうやら 本物のようだな。
It looks like the real thing.
(ヤマト)ここか？
This is the place, huh...?
The entrance is straight ahead
beneath that rocky area.
入り口は 正面にある
あの岩場の下だ。
もしかしたら あの下に…。
Could it be that...
サスケが…。
Sasuke's under there...?
There's a good possibility.
可能性は 十分あるわね。
少なくとも なんらかの
手がかりはあるはずだよ。
At the very least, there should
be clues of some kind.
よし 行くってばよ！
All right! Let's go!
ちょっと待って…。
Just a minute.
行くのは
これを飲んでからだよ… ナルト。
Go after you swallow this,
Naruto.
大丈夫 心配はいらないよ。
It's okay!
You don't need to worry.
ほら サクラもだ。
Here. You, too, Sakura.
もし バラバラになったとしても➡
Now even if we get separated,
これで
キミたちの居場所が すぐわかる。
I'll know where you guys are
right away.
えっ…。
マジで!?
N-No way!
そんなことが…。
Seriously?!
これって…。
What is this?
この種は 簡単に言うと
追跡用の発信機だよ。
Stated simply, this seed is
a transmitter used for tracking.
ボクのチャクラとだけ 共鳴する忍具だ。
It's a Ninja Tool that resonates
only with my Chakra.
(ヤマト)サイの服と食事に
仕込んでおいたのと 同じやつさ。
It's the same thing I placed
in Sai's clothing and food.
サイの服と食事に…？
In Sai's clothing...and food?
うん。
これを…。
This seed...
そっか それで
ここまで追跡できたんだ。
I get it. That's how you were able
to track him this far.
ヤマト隊長ってば
いつの間に そんなこと…。
When did you do that,
Captain Yamato?
覚えてる？
温泉で ボク 先に上がったろ？
Do you remember when
I got out of the hot spring first?
そういえば…。
Come to think of it...
((ヤマト : ボクは 先に上がるからね))
I'm getting out now.
確かに
先に上がってったってばよ。
You certainly did get out first!
なんで ボクが わざわざ
自腹を切って➡
Now you know why
I went to the trouble
of letting you guys enjoy...
キミたちに 豪華な食事と温泉を
堪能させたか…➡
the hot springs and magnificent food
at my expense, right?
これでわかっただろ？
ただ 親睦をはかるためだけじゃ
なかったってわけね。
It wasn't just
to improve our rapport, huh?
特に サイに関しては注意するよう➡
And Lady Tsunade told me...
to take particular caution
in regards to Sai.
綱手様に言われてたしね。
((綱手 : もう１人 あの
暗部養成部門 「根」から➡
An additional member...
a new recruit from
the Anbu Black Ops Training Division...
新人が １人 カカシ班に配属される。
will be dispatched
to Team Kakashi...
ただ…。
なんです？
However...
What is it?
(ソイツの行動には
注意を払っておけ))
Keep a close watch
on his actions...
(ヤマト)まさに そのとおりだった。
And she was right.
((サクラ : すご～い！
Wow!
(うまそう！))
Man, it sure looks good...
I'm glad I took care
of things ahead of time.
(ヤマト)早めに手を打っておいて
よかった。
…と そんなことより
すぐ それ飲んで。
But never mind that.
Swallow that quickly.
Got it!
わかったわ。
よし… じゃあ ２人とも いくよ！
All right!
Let's get going, you two.
オッス！
はい！
- Okay!
- Right!
あの…。
ん？
Excuse me...
Hmm?
このアジトにいる 他の皆さんにも➡
I would like to say hello
to all the others here
in this hideout.
挨拶しておきたいのですが…。
その必要はないよ。
That won't be necessary.
正確には 今はムリだ。
To be precise,
you can't right now.
今 ここにいる大蛇丸様の部下は➡
This is because
the only subordinates here...
ボクとサスケ君だけだからね。
right now are Sasuke and myself.
人の気配は
ほとんど感じられない。
I can barely feel
the presence of anyone.
敵の数は ごくわずかと
考えていいだろう。
I think it's safe to assume there
are not that many enemies at all.
だからといって
気を抜かないように。
Even so, make sure
you don't let your guard down!
相手は大蛇丸だし
サイも 敵側についたと➡
Our opponent is Orochimaru,
and we can assume that Sai
has defected to the enemy's side.
考えるべきだろうしね。
潜入隊列は ボク サクラ ナルトの順だ。
The formation for infiltration will be
in the following order:
me, Sakura, and Naruto.
潜入方法は？
How will we infiltrate?
定石どおり
土遁で地下から近づく。
We'll go by the book...
and infiltrate from underground
using Earth Style.
まずは このあたりから
縦穴を開けていこう。
First, we'll open up
a pit in this area.
ある程度 掘り進んだら➡
And then, once we've made
a degree of progress digging...
あの入り口のある岩場に向かって
横穴を開け➡
we'll move forward little by little
by digging a tunnel...
少しずつ進むよ。
heading for that rocky area
where the entrance is.
はい。
うん わかったってばよ！
Right!
Okay, understood.
それじゃ 始めるよ。
Okay, let's begin.
When I give the signal,
come down in order!
合図をしたら
順番に下りてきてくれ。
それじゃ いくよ！
Okay, here we go!
Let's go, Naruto!
いくわよ ナルト！
Right!
おう！
We finally did it...
《やっと見つけたぞ…。
お前を！》
We found you.
Okay, come on inside...
さぁ 中へ。
This is your room.
ここがキミの部屋だ。
何もない 殺風景なところだが
勘弁してくれ。
Sorry about this place being
so dull with nothing in it.
トイレは その奥だ。
The bathroom is in the back.
用がないときは
ここで おとなしくしていてくれ。
When you don't have
anything to do...
stay in here nice and quiet.
何かあれば こちらから
声をかける。
We'll let you know from our end
if something comes up.
Sorry, but I'll be locking the door
from the outside for now.
悪いけど 一応 外から
鍵をかけさせてもらうよ。
キミは ほら… わかるだろう？
After all, you're...
You know, right?
やはりアジトは
岩に囲まれてるみたいだね。
It appears the hideout...
is surrounded by rocks,
just as I thought...
こんなの すぐに
ぶっ壊してやるってばよ！
I'll smash this thing right away!
With my Rasengan!
オレの螺旋丸で！
ちょい待ち…。
Just a minute!
そんな大きな術したら
すぐに敵に気づかれるでしょ！
The enemy will notice us immediately
if you use a big Jutsu like that!
えっ…。
Infiltration must be done
quietly all the way...
(ヤマト)潜入は あくまで音もなく…。
But how do we do that...?
でも どうやって？
Here it is!
あった…。
The harder the rock...
(ヤマト)硬い岩ほど…。
小さな亀裂に
少し力を加えただけで…。
by applying just a little force
to a small crack...
Look, just like this.
ほら このとおり！
Wow!
へぇ～。
Now, please limit your use
of Chakra from here on.
さて ここから先は
チャクラの使用も制限させてくれ。
大蛇丸に気づかれてしまうからね。
Orochimaru will notice that
we're here, after all.
では いくよ！
Okay, let's go.
A successful infiltration,
more or less.
とりあえずは潜入成功ね！
First, we need to find Sai.
まずは サイを捜す。
こっちだよ！
This way.
Now then, if I don't get right
to making the Bingo Book...
さてと さっさとビンゴブックを
作っておかないと➡
また大蛇丸様に小言を…。
Master Orochimaru
will scold me again.
フッ… Ａ型のほうが
部下にむいているとも➡
He'll probably tell me people
with A type blood...
are better suited to be subordinates
if I do stuff like this.
言われそうだな これじゃ…。
Clear. Let's go.
大丈夫… いくよ！
もう少し…！
We're almost there...
(サクラ)前回に引き続き
サスケ君を振り返るわ！
一見 復讐者という立場を➡
忘れたように見えた
サスケ君だったけど➡
イタチとの再会が
サスケ君の心を変えてしまった。
((今までオレは 何をしていたんだ!?
(イタチ)
なぜ弱いか… 足りないからだ。
In the Foundation,
(憎しみが…))
there were many who came
from broken families...
(サクラ)イタチを倒す力を得るため➡
brought about by battle.
すべてのつながりを断ち切って➡
My older brother was one of those
with whom I became close,
里を抜け 大蛇丸のもとへ
走ってしまうの…。
like a real brother.
I was planning on giving him
this picture book.
((お前は 大蛇丸なんかには
やらねえってばよ～！
初めから一人きりだったテメエに➡
But ever since that day,
I haven't been able to remember...
(オレの何がわかるってんだ！))
what picture I was going to draw
for the final facing pages.
(サクラ)ナルトの命懸けの説得でさえ➡
サスケ君を止めることは
できなかった。
(サクラ)今も 自分が
大蛇丸の器になろうと➡
かまわないと思っているはず。
それでも 私たちは
絶対 サスケ君を➡
とりもどしてみせるわ！
それでは また!!